http://congress.indiana.edu/privacy

HomePrivacy NoticePrivacy NoticeEffective: 2018-05-01ApplicabilityThis privacy notice applies only to the Center on Representative Government (https://corg.iu.edu) and explains our practices concerning the collection, use, and disclosure of visitor information. Visitor information collected by Center on Representative Government will be used only as outlined in this privacy notice.Other units at the university may collect and use visitor information in different ways. Therefore, visitors to other university websites should review the privacy notices for the particular sites they visit. Center on Representative Government is not responsible for the content of other websites or for the privacy practices of websites outside the scope of this notice.ChangesBecause Internet technologies continue to evolve rapidly, Center on Representative Government may make appropriate changes to this notice in the future. Any such changes will be consistent with our commitment to respecting visitor privacy, and will be clearly posted in a revised privacy notice.Collection and UsePassive/Automatic CollectionWhen you view pages on our site, the web server automatically collects certain technical information from your computer and about your connection.This site is hosted on Webserve, a shared web–hosting environment provided by IU’s University Information Technology Services. For more information about privacy practices related to Webserve, read the Webserve Privacy Notice Supplement.In addition to any information collected by Webserve, our server and/or site collects the following:your IP addressthe domain name from which you visit our siteuser-specific information on which pages are visitedaggregate information on pages visitedthe referring websitethe date and time of visitthe duration of visityour browser typeyour screen resolutionContinued use of our website indicates consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of this information as described in this notice.This technical information is not retained or utilized.Active/Manual/Voluntary CollectionWe will not attempt to collect any information from you through the use of forms or other type of manual input.Information UsageThis information is:used for internal review and is then discardedInformation Used For ContactIf you supply us with your postal/mailing address:You will only receive the information for which you provided us your address.Information SharingWe do not share any aggregate, non-personally identifiable information with other entities or organizations.We do not share any personally identifiable information with other entities or organizations, except when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our website and applicable laws, or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our website.Except as described above, we will not share any information with any party for any reason.Except as provided in the Disclosure of Information section below, we do not attempt to use the technical information discussed in this section to identify individual visitors.CookiesA cookie is a small data file that is written to your hard drive that contains information about your visit to a web page. If you prefer not to receive cookies, you may configure your browser not to accept them at all, or to notify and require approval before accepting new cookies. Some web pages/sites may not function properly if the cookies are turned off, or you may have to provide the same information each time you visit those pages.Our site does not use cookies to store information about your actions or choices on pages associated with our site.ChildrenThis site is not directed to children under 13 years of age, does not sell products or services intended for purchase by children, and does not knowingly collect or store any personal information, even in aggregate, about children under the age of 13. We encourage parents and teachers to be involved in children’s Internet explorations. It is particularly important for parents to guide their children when they are asked to provide personal information online.Use of Third Party ServicesThis website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses cookies (described above) to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including possibly your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google.For more information, please visit Google’s Privacy Policy.Social MediaThird-party social media sites may collect information from this site. Indiana University is not responsible for their privacy practices. This site embeds features from third party social media sites, including:Facebook (visit Facebook's privacy policy at: https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation)Twitter (visit Twitter's privacy policy at: https://twitter.com/en/privacy)Disclosure of InformationWe may share some aggregate information with other appropriate university personnel and units to ensure the quality, functionality, and security of our website/application.Any other disclosure—with appropriate external parties such as law enforcement agencies—will be done in accordance with all applicable laws and university policies in order to investigate and respond to suspected violations of law or university policy.SecurityDue to the rapidly evolving nature of information technologies, no transmission of information over the Internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure. While Indiana University is committed to protecting user privacy, IU cannot guarantee the security of any information users transmit to university sites, and users do so at their own risk.We will comply with all applicable federal, state and local laws regarding the privacy and security of user information.Links to non-university sitesIndiana University is not responsible for the availability, content, or privacy practices of non-university sites. Non-university sites are not bound by this site privacy notice policy and may or may not have their own privacy policies.Privacy Notice ChangesFrom time to time, we may use visitor information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice.Only data collected from the time of the policy change forward will be used for these new purposes. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our website periodically.Contact InformationIf you have questions or concerns about this policy, please contact us.Center on Representative GovernmentATTN: Valerie Pena201 N. Indiana Ave.BLOOMINGTON, IN 47405corg@indiana.edu(812) 856-4706If you feel as though this site’s privacy practices differ from the information stated, you may contact us at the listed address or phone number.If you feel that this site is not following its stated policy and communicating with the owner of this site does not resolve the matter, or if you have general questions or concerns about privacy or information technology policy at Indiana University, please contact the chief privacy officer through the University Information Policy Office, 812-855-UIPO, privacy@iu.edu.
Center on Representative Government social media channels
Twitter
Facebook
YouTube
COMMENTS ON CONGRESS
The Pandemic Lays Bare Our Information Problems
Election Takeaways
What Helps Voters Decide?
